Ujjwal Sharma

Front-End Software Developer

µ ujjwal158b@gmail.com

+919643636842

(ujjwalsharma.dev



github.com/us0610

Relevant Experience

Front-end Developer @ TheDefiNetwork

September 2021 - November 2022 // California, USA (remotely)

- Worked on several projects and did debugging on their flagship application "Dropspace".
- Created more than 30 projects in webflow using custom code.
- Worked with several clients and wrote effecient and performant code for their websites.
- Worked with variety of different languages, frameworks and CMS systems such as Javascript, Typescript, PHP, NodeJs, React, NextJs, Prismic, Webflow, Finsweet library etc.

Freelance @ Upwork

May 2020 - Present // New Delhi, India

- Created many complex e-commerce websites using webflow and Javascript, HTML, CSS.
- Created 3 templates including an e-commerce store, personal portfolio website and a web novel.
- Worked with various integrations like Zapier, Foxycart, F'insweet library etc.

Skills

Programming Languages

Javascript, Typescript, HTML, CSS/SCSS, Dart (flutter), C, Java, C++, PHP, PUG

Libraries & Frameworks

ReactJs, NextJs, GatsbyJs, Express, React Native, NodeJs, GSAP

Tools & Platforms

Git, Netlify, Vercel, Vite, Parcel, Flrebase, Shopify, Webflow, Contentful, Prismic, Wordpress

Design

Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD

Education

Indra Gandhi National Open University

January 2021 - Present

BCA full form Bachelor of Computer Application is a 3-year undergraduate course that imparts knowledge on the basics of computer application and software development. BCA subjects include database management systems, software engineering, operating systems, web technology, and computer languages such as Jvascript, HTML, C, C++, and Java.

Bio

Hi my name is Ujjwal sharma, I am 21 years old. I currently live in New Delhi, India. I am pursuing bachelor's of computer applications.

Projects

Realtor

Realtor is a real-estate app. Users can search for properties and sort them out using the filter system of the app.

Web Novel

A webflow template which is heavily custom coded and fully managed by webflow's CMS system. Any author/user can use this template to publish their own web-novel / comic. It has dedicated chapter index silder at the bottom so users can guide through different chapters. It has sorting as well as saving relevant data capabilities.

MantraLabs

An e-commerce store built in webflow which is heavily custom coded. The website contains many elements of a proper store, including many different widgets multiple checkouts depending on quantity, subscription model etc.

Expense Tracker

A minimal expense tracker app, in which user can add expenses, incomes, edit them delete

them and can even sort them out based on date, total income, total expenses.

(There are more projects on my personal portfolio website. You can check

(Thank you for taking your time to read my CV.)